A Guide to the Dr. Norma M. Goode Papers 1981-1997
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
Dr. Norma M. Goode Papers 1981-1997
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
MS-0015
2.5 linear feet.
Dr. Norma M. Goode
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Received from Dr. Goode.
Biographical/Historical Information
Dr. Norma M. Goode was a 1949 graduate of Virginia Union and came back circa 1972 as a Social Work professor and later served as division chair in the Office of Academic Affairs. She earned an MSW at Virginia Commonwealth University and a PhD at the University of Minnesota. Her specialty was gerontology. During the years 1985-87, Goode was acting director of the university's Continuing Education program. Upon her retirement circa 1990, she held the rank of full professor.
Scope and Content Information
These papers document Goode's involvement with the Women's Auxiliary or Deaconess' group, comprising meeting minutes and committee reports from the early 1980s to the mid 1990s. Mostly paper records, there are 13 audiocassette tapes with meetings recorded on them from the early 1990s.
Arrangement
Collection is arranged alphabetical and then chronological.
Contents List
- Series 1. Women's Auxiliary to the Deacon's Conference of Richmond and Vicinity
  - Applications for Membership 1982-1984 (Box 1)
  - Committee Reports 1981-1995 (Box 1)
  - Executive Board 1985-1992, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Financial Reports 1991 (Box 1)
  - Handbook 1994 (Box 1)
  - Membership Lists 1993-1997 (Box 1)
  - Minutes 1982-1997 (Box 1)
  - National Convention 1989-1992, 1998 (Box 1)
  - News Clippings (Box 1)
  - Photos (Box 1)
  - Post-Meeting Reports 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - Post-Meeting Reports 1986-1998 (Box 2)
  - State Convention 1988-1993 (Box 2)
  - Thank-you Notes (Box 2)
  - Youth Department (Box 2)
  - Non-file records (Box 2)
  - Recorded meetings 1993-1994 (Box 2)
  - Notebook, member Reports 1985-1988 (Box 2)
  - Notebook, Monthly Reports 1985-1988 (Box 2)